{"questions":[{"question":"Which of the following does not represent the Agile methodology? ","level":"Medium","answers":["The software delievery happens all at once at the end","First step is to sit down with the client and make user stories","It uses an iterative approach","The requirements may change"],"num_of_correct_answers":2,"ID":1,"correct_ans":1,"num_of_answers":3},{"question":"User stories are made in order for: ","level":"Easy","answers":["Communicating and bonding with the clients","The clients to capture a description of a software feature from an end-user perspective ","Getting a general notion of what the system should look like","The clients to let us know about their personal stories"],"num_of_correct_answers":0,"ID":2,"correct_ans":2,"num_of_answers":1},{"question":"What are the requirements validation techniques?","level":"Medium","answers":["Tracing, Prototyping, Evaluating","Requirement reviews, user stories, googling","Usability testing, peer review, code review","Requirement reviews, Prototyping, Test-case generation"],"num_of_correct_answers":3,"ID":3,"correct_ans":4,"num_of_answers":5},{"question":"The frame story specified requirement x. In the SRS requirement x appeared only partially (there were missing details). What kind of requirements� error is it?(","level":"Easy","answers":["Partial Requirements","Missing Requirements","Contradicting Requirements","Excess Requirements"],"num_of_correct_answers":3,"ID":4,"correct_ans":1,"num_of_answers":4},{"question":"What is not one of the Code Review�s Goals?","level":"Easy","answers":["Backup","Comment and Coding Conventions","Thread Safety","Resource leaks"],"num_of_correct_answers":1,"ID":5,"correct_ans":1,"num_of_answers":2},{"question":"Which of the following is not a type of review?","level":"Easy","answers":["Code Review","Product Approval","Peer review","Branching Review"],"num_of_correct_answers":1,"ID":6,"correct_ans":4,"num_of_answers":4},{"question":"Which one is not a phase of system�s life cycle?  ","level":"Medium","answers":["Drill down","Evolution","Servicing","Phase-out"],"num_of_correct_answers":3,"ID":7,"correct_ans":1,"num_of_answers":4},{"question":"Which one is NOT an architectural pattern?  ","level":"Easy","answers":["MVC","BIM","Layered architecture ","Client server"],"num_of_correct_answers":1,"ID":8,"correct_ans":2,"num_of_answers":4},{"question":"Which of the following is the most correct sentence about testing?   ","level":"Hard","answers":["Test-first development is an approach to development whereby tests are written after the code to be tested.","Stubs is used in bottom-up integration and driver in top down integration","The acceptance testing is after the system is deployed in operational environment. ","Stubs and drivers are dummy modules."],"num_of_correct_answers":0,"ID":9,"correct_ans":4,"num_of_answers":2},{"question":"Black box testing and white box testing are?  ","level":"Hard","answers":["In black box testing the functionality of the software is known and in white box testing its not","In white box testing the software structure is known and black box it's not.","Black box testing and white box testing are the same.","Back box testing is done during the night and white box during the day. "],"num_of_correct_answers":1,"ID":10,"correct_ans":2,"num_of_answers":6},{"question":"What is the correct order of testing?       ","level":"Medium","answers":["Alpha testing, Beta testing, Acceptance testing.","Acceptance testing, Alpha testing, Beta testing.","Beta testing, Acceptance testing, Alpha testing.","Alpha, beta and acceptance testing are done simultaneously."],"num_of_correct_answers":2,"ID":11,"correct_ans":1,"num_of_answers":2},{"question":"Which of the following is not a kind of maintenance?           ","level":"Hard","answers":["Corrective maintenance.","Adaptive maintenance.","Perfective maintenance.","Regression fault maintenance."],"num_of_correct_answers":1,"ID":12,"correct_ans":4,"num_of_answers":4},{"question":"Which of the following is the most correct answer? ","level":"Hard","answers":["Corrective maintenance is modifying the system to satisfy new requirements","Perfective maintenance is adapting software to a different operating environment","None of the answers is correct.","Adaptive maintenance is changing a system to fix bugs."],"num_of_correct_answers":6,"ID":13,"correct_ans":3,"num_of_answers":9},{"question":"Maintenance predictions are not influenced by?         ","level":"Medium","answers":["Number and complexity of system interfaces.","Number of inherently volatile system requirements.","The business processes where the system is used","Number of code lines the system has."],"num_of_correct_answers":1,"ID":14,"correct_ans":4,"num_of_answers":4},{"question":"hi","level":"Easy","answers":["1","2","3","4"],"num_of_correct_answers":1,"ID":15,"correct_ans":3,"num_of_answers":2}]}